A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Lady Arachne. I can't feel her soul.
My mistress has lost to me forever.
Kumbach.
Kumbach!
I'm falling, coming to my shadow
息をひそめて
待っている Dead Dream Life
Don't scare me,君が望めば
どんな世界も
その目に映せるから
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
怖い夢だとしても
全部君のために
星を砕ぎ
飾り付けた
Black paper
信じてくれたなら
When you lost it
We are young
Forever with your soul
見上げれば輝く
月のように
Baka
Are you sure you're ready for this?
I'm ready for anything
Lord Death can't fight anymore
It's up to us now
Ashura wakes
To the end of the world
Is that him?
Yes, it's the Kishin
You can almost feel the evil coming from him
Let's get him, Tsubaki
Right
Hold on a sec, Blackstar
I'm coming
No, Mufune
You need to take that midget
And get out of here quickly
Hey, you dummy
Take that back
Angie's not a midget
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yeah, I am
I'm the man who's gonna surpass God, remember?
Black Star
Not good
Not at all
What is that thing?
A barrier
A barrier?
The Kishin was badly injured
During his fight with Lord Death
He's going into a deep sleep
To heal
No, he can't
If he does, then that means
The madness wavelength will continue to expand
His insanity will take over the world
Without him lifting a finger
No, it won't
I can't sit here and let that happen
Liz
Patty
Yeah
I will take my father's place
He can't fight now, but I can
As a grim reaper
I will protect this world
Kid, where are you going?
You can't just run off
Come back here!
You gonna charge in there without a Meister?
What good will that do?
Move it, move it, move it, move it, move it, move it, move it!
Ahhhhhh...
Yoh, Maka, gettin' here a little late, aren't ya?
Sorry, I had some things to take care of
So we all began this battle in different places
And yet here we are back together at the end of it
Yep, I'm not complaining
Yeah, neither am I.
All right. Keep a tight rein on your souls at all times.
Do not let down your guard.
If you do, the madness will consume you.
We can't afford to let that happen.
We know. He got me last time.
But this time, I'm gonna make him pay!
To preserve this world and to avenge my father,
I will beat you.
If we manage to make it out of this alive,
something tells me ghosts won't scare me so much anymore.
Wow! That would make you as strong as the Grim Reaper.
Now, now, Patty. Let's not get too carried away, okay?
I'm not gonna be volunteering for that job anytime soon.
Can I?
Black Star. Yeah?
Is today the day?
Will this be the moment when you surpass God?
Yeah. Just watch me.
Okay, guys. Are we ready?
Hey, wait a second. That's not what he looked like a minute ago.
Yeah, he got a lot bigger. No fair.
He must have killed Arachne and swallowed her soul.
I couldn't care less what you look like, Chishin.
I'm still gonna destroy you. Got it?
Insects. Yummy. Come closer, little insects.
Listen up.
Soul is about to play. Everyone ready?
Everyone ready?
Showtime. Now. Soul. Play it.
Impossible. That girl is combining two incredible powers.
Black Blood and Genie Hunter working together?
Let's go!
His skin is as hard as armor.
Our attacks are working, though. Let's keep it coming.
You ready to go, Maka?
Damn! Are you sure this is working?
Yes, I'm positive. Just look around you.
Up there!
The barrier he's set up is starting to weaken.
That's proof we're doing something.
It does look a bit thinner.
That's good, right?
We're resonating well together, too.
If we keep this up, we can beat him.
What's happening?
Something's off.
It feels like I'm forgetting something important.
Something I need to remember.
But what is it?
Keep going.
Let's pick up the tempo!
Hey, Soul, are you even listening to us?
Quit your whining. Of course I'm listening to you.
You guys just shut up and pay attention to my playing.
Faster now!
Get ready!
We're building to the climax!
Fire jet cannon!
Fire jet cannon.
Genie!
Soul!
This is the end of the line, Soul.
You played your last tune.
It's my world now.
Soul!
That's impossible. No way.
He's still as good as new.
There's no sign of a single injury.
The surgery went well. We just need to keep him stable. Given enough time, he should make a full recovery.
We just need to keep him stable.
Given enough time, he should make a full recovery.
Yeah, that's good to hear.
But still...
Still what?
It's just that I said something I'll never be able to take back.
I told Crona I didn't trust him,
that I never would again unless we recovered you.
I was there with him the whole time,
but I couldn't keep him from getting injured.
He's hurt because I forced him into fighting Medusa.
It's all my fault.
So why not tell him that?
Crona's going to be all right.
You can tell him how you feel when he wakes up.
I'm sure he'll forgive you.
Crona, are you okay?
Crona!
Can't stay. I have to go.
I have to go find Maka.
You're persistent.
How long are you going to keep this up?
They've obviously betrayed you.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm going to pay them back with interest.
But before I do that, I'm going to take care of you!
Who's next on this list?
Who do you think?
It'll be that old hag Arach...
Oh, really?
Well, I guess you can always try.
But I think you'll find it's a little too late for that.
What's that supposed to mean?
Someone beat you to it.
She's already dead.
She is?
Haven't you noticed you're the only one still fighting?
Everyone else has begun to retreat.
Arachnophobia's destroyed.
You're alone.
There's no way...
You have a decision to make.
DWMA troops will be flooding in here soon.
You can run or fight all of them by yourself.
Fine, you lucky punk.
I'll go easy on you today.
Cat got your tongue?
Just remember one thing.
I'm still going to kick your ass someday!
Look at that.
I know you so well, I can predict your foul language.
Shut up!
I've had enough, you damn priest!
The next time we meet, you're not going to be so lucky!
Remember that!
What is it?
A barrier the Kishin created.
We think it's similar to the Death Room.
Impenetrable from the outside.
I see.
The spread of the madness hasn't even slowed down.
I don't know what more we can try to do.
We made Death City move, but we still couldn't beat the Kishin.
Fools!
What do you use your eyes for?
Decoration?
His eyes look like a failed arts and crafts project, and he's asking me that?
There's still a slight hope.
What are you talking about?
Three Meisters made it inside.
Death the Kid's there, with Blackstar, and Maka Albarn.
They all have their weapons with them.
The battle's not over.
We've still got a chance.
Maka and the others are in there?
Victory still isn't very likely.
But if Maka can use her Genie Hunter move, then maybe.
Yes, you're right.
If Maka can harness enough power at the right time, then she might be able to defeat the Kishin.
That doesn't change anything for us up here.
Huh?
All we can do is stand here and watch.
Sol!
Wake up!
What's going on?
What happened?
Why is he just lying there?
I don't understand what's wrong with him either.
Maybe.
Your friend bit off more than he could chew.
He what?
What the?
Where did he go?
He did whatever he had to in order to push all your powers to their maximum potential,
which increased the burden on himself.
This has been a long time coming indeed.
Because of the black blood he has in his body?
Every power comes with a price.
In this case, it was his sanity, but he wasn't willing to give it up.
He wanted both.
If he had just given in, everything would have been different.
If he'd done that, he would have known a life without fear.
But he refused, and chose instead to pointlessly destroy himself.
Shut up, jackass.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Quiet.
He's trying to provoke us.
We can't afford to get caught up in that.
Why should I care?
This is my show.
He can say anything he wants to me.
One way or another, he's still gonna die today!
No way!
He did that using only his wavelength?
I shouldn't be surprised.
It is Blackstar.
But we still have a problem.
With Soul Out cold, we have no one to synchronize our wavelengths.
Kid, we've got to keep going!
Yeah, I know that.
He's not even flinching.
We have to gain some ground before the Kishin decides to strike back at us.
Or we're going to lose.
His pulse is getting weaker.
And he's starting to turn pale.
If this keeps up...
Please, Soul.
Please come back.
What are you doing?
Go get Soul!
Maka, you're the only one who can save him now.
It's all up to you.
Hurry up and bring that idiot back!
Kid, Blackstar.
Are you sure?
Do what you need to.
I promise.
We'll find a way to keep the Kishin back.
What are you talking about?
By the time she's back, it'll be all over.
It's just too bad for you, Maka.
Unfortunately, looks like you're gonna miss the chance to watch my best show yet.
Foolish children.
You can't save him.
Stop talking.
This decision doesn't concern you even in the slightest.
You should shut up and start getting ready to fight me!
Good luck.
Soul.
I'm coming for you.
It's weak, but I can feel it.
Soul's wavelength.
Soul.
That sound. I hear a piano. That soul.
I hear a piano.
That soul.
I've been waiting for you, Maka.
Is it you?
Yeah. Who are you expecting?
Are you okay?
I'm so bored.
Now, die.
I'm not gonna let you hurt them. Ever. See, I made a promise to a friend of mine.
We keep the promises we make. It's an academy thing. You wouldn't get it.
Kishin Asherah, you die today.
Kishin Asherah
demons
Kishin Ashereah
Shimidona
Y幾
Kishin Asherah
Yahoo! Let's go, Tsubaki! It's our time to shine!
Shine? Yeah, sure.
What's up with you? You don't seem as chipper as normal.
It's something that's been bothering me for a while now.
Do you really want to hear about it?
Uh, sure. Why not?
We weapons hardly get any lines when we're in our non-human forms.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, Sink or Swim,
the men who transcend the gods?
A few more lines wouldn't hurt.